<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NewPlans</title>
    <description>A minimal blog template, build with Jekyll.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 16:11:32 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 16:11:32 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>AARRR Framework 란</title>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&quot;aarrr이란&quot;&gt;AARRR이란&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Priates Metrics(해적 지표)라고도 불리며 주로 리소스가 한정된 스타트업에서 사용한다. AARRR프레임을 통해 고객의 유입부터 활동, 재방문, 추천, 구매에 이르는 각 단계를 분석해 효율적으로 개선할 수 있도록 도와준다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;aarrr-단계별-핵심-지표&quot;&gt;AARRR 단계별 핵심 지표&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/05/aarrr.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;aarrr&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Acquisition - 획득, 유치&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;어떻게 우리 서비스를 접하고 있는지&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Activation - 활동&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;사용자가 처음 서비스를 이용할 때 긍정적인 경험을 제공하는가&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Retention - 유지 또는 재방문&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;이후의 서비스 재사용률은 어떻게 되는가&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Refferal - 추천&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;사용자가 자발적 바이럴, 공유를 일으키고 있는가&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Revenue - 구매&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;최종 목적(매출)으로 연결되고 있는가&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;구체적으로&quot;&gt;구체적으로&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;##### Acquisiton&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;우리 서비스의 첫 방문자들이 어떤 채널을 통해 유입되었는지 측정한다. 페이스북 / 구글 광고 또는 검색 최적화를 주로 사용한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;측정 지표: 신규방문자 수&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;activation&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Activation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;유입된 고객이 우리 서비스를 얼마나 활발히 이용하고 있는지 측정한다. 서비스를 이용하는 고객들이 바로 이탈하지 않고 오래 머물수록 좋기때문에 회원가입이나 컨텐츠 구독처럼 머물러 있는 시간이나 다른 컨텐츠의 소비, 참여 등이 활성화의 기준이 된다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;측정지표: 이탈률(Bounce Rate) / PV(Page View) / 세션당 페이지수 / 회원가입 / 구독 / 체류시간&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;__retenrion-__&quot;&gt;__Retenrion __&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;서비스를 한 번 이용했던 고객이 재방문하여 다른 컨텐츠를 소비하거나 참여하는 것을 말한다. 재방문율이 높다는 것은 그만큼 서비스에 대한 만족감을 높다는 것을 의미 할 수 있기 때문에 중요한 수치입니다. 재방문을 유도하기 위해 주로 이메일이나, 구독, 푸쉬, 쿠폰 발행 등의 방법을 사용한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;측정지표: 재방문율(Retention Rate) / DAU / MAU 사용&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;refferal&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Refferal&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;바이럴 마케팅이 대표적인 방법이다. 주로 지인의 추천이나 자주가는 커뮤니티 또는 블로그 등의 추천을 통해 간접 경험 후 서비스를 가입하거나 이용하게 된다. 어떤 광고보다 효과가 좋은건 &lt;em&gt;지인의 추천&lt;/em&gt; 이다. 내 서비스 이용자인 고객들이 지인에게 추천을 할 수 있도록 해야한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;측정지표: 공유 / 댓글 / 태그 / 바이럴 계수&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;revenue&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Revenue&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;p&gt;최종적 목표인 구매율을 높이기 위한 방법이다. 아무리 측정을 잘했더라도 구매가 이루어지지 않은면 비즈니스가 되지 않는다. 각 지표사이의 상관 관계를 분석하여 구매율을 높이는 것이 AARRRDML 목적이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;측정지표: 전환율 / 객단가 / CLV&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;단어-정리&quot;&gt;단어 정리&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DAU (Daily Active User) 일간 순수 이용자&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;사용자를 이해하는 중요한 기본 관리 지표.  유저해빗에서는 오늘의 순사용자도 1시간 간격으로 실시간 집계하여 표시한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;MAU (Monthly Active User) 월간 순수 이용자&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;일반적으로 이전 30일을 기준으로 측정하거나 1일부터 말일을 기준으로 측정한다. 유저해빗에서는 일수와 상관없이 월을 기준으로 사용자수 측정&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;유저해빗(User Habit)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;깊이 있는 사용자 행동 분석을 제공하는 새로운 종류의 데이터 분석 서비스&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CLV (Customer Lifetime Value) 고객 생애 가치&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;비즈니스와의 관계를 통해 소비자가 기업에 기여하는 총 가치를 말한다.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;객단가&lt;/p&gt;

    &lt;p&gt;고객이 1회 구매 시 평균적으로 결제하는 금애글 의미한다. 여러 상품을 판매하는 경우는 상품별로 파악하는 것이 좋다.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2020 02:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//aarrr-funnel/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//aarrr-funnel/</guid>
        
        <category>마케팅</category>
        
        <category>marketing</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 비전공자</category>
        
        <category>aarrr</category>
        
        <category>funnel</category>
        
        
        <category>마케팅</category>
        
        <category>marketing</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 비전공자</category>
        
        <category>aarrr</category>
        
        <category>funnel</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>비 전공자가 알고있으면 좋겠는 마케팅 용어</title>
        <description>&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Landing Page 랜딩페이지&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;검색 광고의 텍스트나 배너 광고를 클릭 했을 때 연결되는 페이지를 의미한다.  랜딩페이지는 주로 광고주의 홈페이지나 이벤트 페이지로 연결되는 경우가 대부분이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Impression 노출&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;광고 노출 횟수를 말하며 웹사이트가 열려 배너광고가 한 번 노출될 때 한 번의 카운팅을 합니다. 특히 웹페이지의 한 지면에는 디자인에 따라 여러 개의 광고가 들어갈 수 있기 때문에, 단위 시간당 웹페이지보다는 단위 시간당 광고 뷰로 더 많이 표기합니다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Retargeting Advertising 리타겟팅 광고&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;광고주의 웹사이트에 방문한 적이 있거나 웹사이트 내의 특정 페이지를 열람한 경험이 있는 소비자에게 광고를 보여주는 방법입니다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Reach 도달률&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;광고에 노출된 타깃의 비율&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;배너 광고든 SNS의 콘텐츠든 특정 메세지가 존재할 때 최소한 한번 또는 그 이상 노출 된 이용자의 수나 퍼센테이지를 말한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;⚠︎ 도달률의 경우 의도한 메시지가 대상에 여러 번 노출되더라도 한번으로 계산을 한다는 점.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reach 1+: 광고에 최소한 한 번 이상 노출된 타깃의 비율&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reach 2+: 광고에 최소한 두 번 이상 노출된 타깃의 비율&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reach 3+: 광고에 최소한 세 번 이상 노출된 타깃의 비율&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CRM ( Customer Relationship Management ) 고객관계관리&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;CPC ( Cost Per Click ) 클릭 당 비용&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;웹 사이트 방문이든 매출이든, 구매 전환을 향상하는데 가장 효과적이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;광고를 클릭하면, 방문자는 기업 웹사이트로 바로 이동이 되며, 기업은 클릭에 대한 비용을 지불한다. 고객이 구매하면, 클릭에 대한 투자의 가치가 실현되는 것이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;구매 전환이나 고객 획득을 목표로 하는 경우, CPC 가격 모델이 최고의 선택이 될 것이다.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CPM ( Cost Per Millium ) 1,000개 노출 당 비용&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;브랜드의 인지도와 참여도를 높이는데 가장 효과적이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;브랜드 가시성을 향상하려면 선택하는 것이 좋음. 어떤 유형의 페이지를 타겟팅할 지 세부적으로 선택이 가능하다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1,000 회의 노출을 구매하는 경우, 웹 전반에서 1,000개의 광고가 표시된 다는 사실을 이해해야 한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CPA (Cost Per Action ) 액션 당 단가&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;소비자가 온라인 상에 노출된 광고를 클릭하고 랜딩페이지에 진입했을 시 광고주가 원하는 특정 행동을 취할 때 과금하는 광고비 책정 방식이다. 주로 구매기준으로 삼지만 회원가입, 이벤트 신청, 다운로드, 어플리케이션 설치 등을 기준으로 삼기도 한다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CTR ( Click - Though Rate ) 노출 대비 클릭 수&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;광고의 노출 횟수 대비 클릭이 일어난 횟수를 나타내는 말이다. 쉽게 말해 광고를 본 사람 중 몇 명이나 해당 광고를 클릭했나를 비율로 나타낸 것이다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;클릭수 / 노출수 x 100&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;CVR ( Conversion  Rate )전환율&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;전환은 광고 등을 통해 사이트를 방문한 사람이 제품 구매, 장바구니 담기, 회원가입, 뉴스레터 신청 등을 &lt;strong&gt;광고주가 의도한 행위를 취하는 것&lt;/strong&gt; 을 뜻한다. 광고의 성과를 파악하는 지표 중 하나라고 표현할 수 있으면 쇼핑몰과 같은 전자상거래 업종을 주로 결제를 전환으로 잡는다.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;전환수 / 유입수 x 100&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;출처&quot;&gt;출처&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.criteo.com/kr/insights/whats-difference-cpc-cpm/&quot;&gt;criteo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.socialmkt.co.kr/475&quot;&gt;소셜마케팅코리아 블로그&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jan 2020 20:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//marketing word_1/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//marketing word_1/</guid>
        
        <category>마케팅</category>
        
        <category>marketing</category>
        
        <category>marketing word</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 비전공자</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 용어</category>
        
        
        <category>마케팅</category>
        
        <category>marketing</category>
        
        <category>marketing word</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 비전공자</category>
        
        <category>마케팅 용어</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Korea Activity - CandlelyU Diffuser</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;make-a-natural-handmade-air-freshener&quot;&gt;Make a Natural Handmade Air Freshener.&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using natural ingredients to freshen the air in your home is a great way to absorb odors and create a nicely scented environment for your family.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Let’s make a ‘Marine’ air freshener!!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step-1-decorate-the-diffuser-vase&quot;&gt;Step 1. Decorate the diffuser vase.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can fill diffuser vase up with various shells, coral reefs, 8 kinds of sand.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tip!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coral reefs and grasses are hard to infix in the sand, so it is recommended to dig them around with tweezers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/03/step1.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;step1&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step2-choose-your-scent&quot;&gt;Step2. Choose Your Scent.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are more than 20 kinds of fragrance oil, and you pick the one you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tip!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I recommend you to pick the strong fragrance because the strong scent is better to spread in the air.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you keep smelling scent, you can get a headache. So, If you have any fragrance you like, I recommend listing them in front of you. And then, Take it again.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/03/step2.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;step2&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;step3--shake-oil-with-the-base&quot;&gt;Step3.  Shake oil with the base.&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grab the container to pour in fragrance oil and base. Lastly, Shake well to mix with the base.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/03/mix.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;step3&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/03/finish.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;img&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;manual&quot;&gt;Manual&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;You can use the handmade air freshener in 7days.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Car - air freshener : With the inner stopper removed and the wooden cap put back on, you turn the bottle over for about 5 seconds to activate the wooden cap and the oil diffuses through the wood&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;precaution&quot;&gt;Precaution&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;when you use it in the stuffy place, you should often air.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Use it leveled off&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adress : 51-34, Galhyeon-ro 29-gil, Eunpyeong-gu, Seoul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hours : Contact host&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Price : 100ml - 30000KRW / 50ml - 25000KRW&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @_candlelyu&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blog: &lt;a href=&quot;https://blog.naver.com/candlely_u&quot;&gt;CandlelyU&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 19:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//CandlelyU Diffuser/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//CandlelyU Diffuser/</guid>
        
        <category>Korea</category>
        
        <category>trip</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel experience</category>
        
        <category>Korea tourist</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel tips</category>
        
        <category>Seoul tour</category>
        
        <category>diffuser</category>
        
        <category>souvenirs</category>
        
        <category>Korea activity</category>
        
        
        <category>korea</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>air freshener</category>
        
        <category>diffuser</category>
        
        <category>souvenirs</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Korea Activity - Simone Handbag Museum</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;simone--handbag-museum&quot;&gt;SIMONE  HANDBAG MUSEUM&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/bag.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;bag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing to take care of when you travel is the passport. Normally, we need to take off the passport cover at the screening, but this passport case is durable that can be easily put in and out so I chose to use it. From now on, I will introduce three places that can do three things at once a day from the museum to the workshop experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the “SIMone Handbag Museum!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/3floor.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;3f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ticket booth and museum is on the third floor, so don’t enter the store as soon as you get in and let’s take the elevator to the third floor. 5000 won only includes admission to the museum; so if you want to experience leather art, let’s get a day pass!!
A day pass is 32000won&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/ticket.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;ticket&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day ticket includes the museum pass, one free drink, and leather art experiences. Due to the drying leather process at the leather art, there are two ways to go to the museum and cafe first, take out coffee, and go to the museum using the time when leather edge dries. Why can’t you go to the museum without going to the cafe? The reason is that the museum is not allowed to bring food into the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/pass&amp;amp;card.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;pass&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose the first way and experienced leather art first. When I first went there, it was a choice of passport cover and card wallet, which is a preference. Next is leather selection. There were many kinds of leather, and you can choose from them what you want to do. There were only those leather skins when I went there, and I think there were slightly different leather skins every day. Once you’ve made your choice, you’re ready! Let’s go back to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/leather.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;leather&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing we did was because the leather is square, so let’s cut it into the passport cover shape frame! You have to be careful when you squeeze things out. You have to cut them with all the strength to make them look pretty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/cut.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cut&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you finish cutting, the next process is the edge coating, which is applied to the cut section with a knife to prevent the tip of the leather from spreading. It folds in half, so only coat the top part. For the side part, it has to be stapled with thread and color it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/glow.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;glow&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the edge coating is completed, you can choose the color (edge paint) to put on the corners. I think it would be better to compare the samples to my work. I chose the opposite color because mine was dark. Because it’s dark inside the bag, and I thought I could find it if the top was bright, so I chose the mustard color that makes it stand out well. I think it’s pretty fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/color.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;color&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The head of the workshop will do it by himself because the length of the workshop experience is set. Then, he recommended painting slightly thicker than the top because it needs to be painted with a second coat and edge paint on the side and the bottom that has not been re-painted. I went to the museum while the edge paint was drying up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/captin.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cap&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is then said that it is better to paint a little thicker than the upper surface because it is doubled to have to paint the side edge and bottom side which are not painted again with edge coat and edge paint. I went to the museum while the edge paint was dry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/aaa.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;3f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The museum consists of two floors in total and each floor has a different feeling. The third floor was avant-garde and had a modern mood, while the fourth floor had a traditional mood in Victorian style. There’s also an audio guide, so let’s rent it if you need it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/4floor.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;4f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I went to the cafe and ordered a drink and waited for a while, I thought it was almost time to dry up, so I went down again. My finished product was in plastic bag. Although it was first to make the leather product, I was happy to see the finished product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/cafe.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cafe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It supposed to enjoy various experiences at a cheap price to fit the blog theme, and with the price of 32,000 won, the museum and leather art were well organized, so you could see, hear and feel about the leather as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adress : 536-17 Sinsa-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hours : Tue - Sat 10:00 - 19:00 / Sun 11:00 - 19:00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets: Only Museum admission 5000KWR / Oneday-Pass 32000KRW (20%off)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tel: +82 2 3444 0912&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @simonehandbagmusenum&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 14:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//simone handbag/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//simone handbag/</guid>
        
        <category>Korea</category>
        
        <category>trip</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel experience</category>
        
        <category>Korea tourist</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel tips</category>
        
        <category>Seoul tour</category>
        
        <category>leather</category>
        
        <category>souvenirs</category>
        
        <category>Korea activity</category>
        
        
        <category>korea</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>leather</category>
        
        <category>museum</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About Newplans</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi. I’m Surim working as a travel planner and activity recommender. I will make you the most unforgettable memory during your trip to Korea. Do you want to know Korea? Participate in many special classes and enjoy your trip! You can also make your own souvenirs. Make special memories of your life!! Here are a couple of things to do in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• One-day class program - making cooking, and art, making perfume, flower class, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Culture class program - making Korean foods, Tempele-stay, street food and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Exercise class program - flying yoga, climbing, body correction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s an activity that I’m interested in my posts, please leave a comment. And, if there is any activity you want to do, please tell me. I respect your opinion. Tell me your route and which day you want to put it in. I’ll help you plan your trip more easily and easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although I still have a small plan, I hope these little plans will be a small gift to you from afar.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//about-newplans-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//about-newplans-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>hobby</category>
        
        <category>korea</category>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
