<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NewPlans</title>
    <description>A minimal blog template, build with Jekyll.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000//</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 15:36:51 +0900</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2019 15:36:51 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v4.0.0</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Korea Activity - Simone Handbag Museum</title>
        <description>&lt;h1 id=&quot;simone--handbag-museum&quot;&gt;SIMONE  HANDBAG MUSEUM&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/bag.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;bag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing to take care of when you travel is the passport. Normally, we need to take off the passport cover at the screening, but this passport case is durable that can be easily put in and out so I chose to use it. From now on, I will introduce three places that can do three things at once a day from the museum to the workshop experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is the “SIMone Handbag Museum!”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/3floor.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;3f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ticket booth and museum is on the third floor, so don’t enter the store as soon as you get in and let’s take the elevator to the third floor. 5000 won only includes admission to the museum; so if you want to experience leather art, let’s get a day pass!!
A day pass is 32000won&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/ticket.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;ticket&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A day ticket includes the museum pass, one free drink, and leather art experiences. Due to the drying leather process at the leather art, there are two ways to go to the museum and cafe first, take out coffee, and go to the museum using the time when leather edge dries. Why can’t you go to the museum without going to the cafe? The reason is that the museum is not allowed to bring food into the museum.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/pass&amp;amp;card.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;pass&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose the first way and experienced leather art first. When I first went there, it was a choice of passport cover and card wallet, which is a preference. Next is leather selection. There were many kinds of leather, and you can choose from them what you want to do. There were only those leather skins when I went there, and I think there were slightly different leather skins every day. Once you’ve made your choice, you’re ready! Let’s go back to work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/leather.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;leather&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first thing we did was because the leather is square, so let’s cut it into the passport cover shape frame! You have to be careful when you squeeze things out. You have to cut them with all the strength to make them look pretty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/cut.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cut&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you finish cutting, the next process is the edge coating, which is applied to the cut section with a knife to prevent the tip of the leather from spreading. It folds in half, so only coat the top part. For the side part, it has to be stapled with thread and color it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/glow.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;glow&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After the edge coating is completed, you can choose the color (edge paint) to put on the corners. I think it would be better to compare the samples to my work. I chose the opposite color because mine was dark. Because it’s dark inside the bag, and I thought I could find it if the top was bright, so I chose the mustard color that makes it stand out well. I think it’s pretty fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/color.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;color&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The head of the workshop will do it by himself because the length of the workshop experience is set. Then, he recommended painting slightly thicker than the top because it needs to be painted with a second coat and edge paint on the side and the bottom that has not been re-painted. I went to the museum while the edge paint was drying up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/captin.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cap&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is then said that it is better to paint a little thicker than the upper surface because it is doubled to have to paint the side edge and bottom side which are not painted again with edge coat and edge paint. I went to the museum while the edge paint was dry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/aaa.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;3f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The museum consists of two floors in total and each floor has a different feeling. The third floor was avant-garde and had a modern mood, while the fourth floor had a traditional mood in Victorian style. There’s also an audio guide, so let’s rent it if you need it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/4floor.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;4f&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I went to the cafe and ordered a drink and waited for a while, I thought it was almost time to dry up, so I went down again. My finished product was in plastic bag. Although it was first to make the leather product, I was happy to see the finished product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/img/post/02/cafe.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;cafe&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It supposed to enjoy various experiences at a cheap price to fit the blog theme, and with the price of 32,000 won, the museum and leather art were well organized, so you could see, hear and feel about the leather as well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;hr /&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adress : 536-17 Sinsa-dong, Gangnam-gu, Seoul&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hours : Tue - Sat 10:00 - 19:00 / Sun 11:00 - 19:00&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tickets: Only Museum admission 5000KWR / Oneday-Pass 32000KRW (20%off)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tel: +82 2 3444 0912&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instagram: @simonehandbagmusenum&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 17 Dec 2019 14:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//simone handbag/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//simone handbag/</guid>
        
        <category>Korea</category>
        
        <category>trip</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel experience</category>
        
        <category>Korea tourist</category>
        
        <category>Korea travel tips</category>
        
        <category>Seoul tour</category>
        
        <category>leather</category>
        
        <category>souvenirs</category>
        
        
        <category>korea</category>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>leather</category>
        
        <category>museum</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>About Newplans</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi. I’m Surim working as a travel planner and activity recommender. I will make you the most unforgettable memory during your trip to Korea. Do you want to know Korea? Participate in many special classes and enjoy your trip! You can also make your own souvenirs. Make special memories of your life!! Here are a couple of things to do in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• One-day class program - making cooking, and art, making perfume, flower class, and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Culture class program - making Korean foods, Tempele-stay, street food and more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Exercise class program - flying yoga, climbing, body correction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there’s an activity that I’m interested in my posts, please leave a comment. And, if there is any activity you want to do, please tell me. I respect your opinion. Tell me your route and which day you want to put it in. I’ll help you plan your trip more easily and easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although I still have a small plan, I hope these little plans will be a small gift to you from afar.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 15:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000//about-newplans-blog/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000//about-newplans-blog/</guid>
        
        <category>travel</category>
        
        <category>hobby</category>
        
        <category>korea</category>
        
        
        <category>Blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
